https://www.melrosewakefield.org/web-privacy-policy/

Hide Search
I'm looking for...
Our Urgent Cares
Tufts Medical Center Community Care offices (formerly HHMA)
VIEW ALL
Tufts Medical Center Community Care (formerly HHMA)
Dec 10
COVID-19 Update: For the safety of patients and visitors, we are restricting visitors effective Dec. 1
Read More
Home / Web Privacy Policy
Home
Web Privacy Policy
MelroseWakefield Healthcare is dedicated to protecting your privacy.
We have created this privacy policy so you can be assured that any information you share with us will remain confidential. The following describes the information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.
Information We Collect
Some features of this website require users to register and provide personal information such as their name, e-mail address or alternate methods of contact such as street address and phone number. This data allows us to provide you with the information you have requested and helps us to develop new features and services that match your needs and interests. If you would prefer not to share this information, you can choose to not use the parts of the website for which registration is required.
MelroseWakefield Healthcare will collect personally identifiable information only with your knowledge and consent. We also collect limited, non-identifiable web traffic information through our website logs to help us understand such things as which sections of our website receive the most traffic and during which hours we receive the most visitors. We use this information only for aggregate reporting. We do not use it to analyze or identify the use of our site by any specific visitor.
Privacy of Information You Provide
Under no circumstances will MelroseWakefield Healthcare disclose your personal information to a third party without your specific consent or as required by law. MelroseWakefield Healthcare will not willfully sell, rent, loan, share, trade, or disclose to third parties any personal information that you have specifically and knowingly provided to the website.
Security Measures
This website contains security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Only authorized individuals have access to the information you provide.
Linked Sites
This website contains links to content that MelroseWakefield Healthcare believes may be of interest to you. MelroseWakefield Healthcare accepts no responsibility for the privacy practices or the content of linked websites.
Disclosure of Ownership and Funding
MelroseWakefield.org is entirely funded by MelroseWakefield Healthcare, and does not accept payment from third-parties for advertising or any other service. MelroseWakefield Healthcare is the sole owner of MelroseWakefield.org and is responsible for the growth, development and maintenance of the site.
Contacting MelroseWakefield Healthcare About this Website
If you have questions about this privacy statement or the practices of this website, please call 781-979-3000 and ask for the marketing department.
Share
Contact Us
We’re here to assist you.
Call 781-979-3021
2018 Annual Report
Growth and Positive Momentum for Our Organization
State-of-the-Art Technology
Growing Neurosurgery Services
New Brand Identity
2018 Highlights
Financial Overview
Newsletters
Coming Soon!
Safe with Us
State’s Reopening
COVID-19 Testing Information
Visitors’ Information
Shop
Take Care of Back Pain
test
Vendor Supplier Information Center
Vital Cardiology Services
Web Privacy Policy
HHVNA Care in the Community (OLD)
About MelroseWakefield Healthcare
Growing with Tufts Medical Center
Administration
Board of Trustees
Physician Leadership
Mission & Vision
Annual Report
Follow us
For Nurses
Wellforce is a health system that is rethinking how academic and community centers, local and national businesses, and technology and service innovators can all work together. So that clinicians can deliver expert care where it's needed most. And so that we can bring wellness back to healthcare, one person at a time.
© 2020 MelroseWakefield Healthcare | 170 Governors Avenue | Medford, MA 02155 | 781-979-3000
MelroseWakefield Healthcare does not discriminate on the basis of race, color, national origin, citizenship, alienage, religion, creed, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, age or disability.
Your privacy is important to us. Learn more about our website privacy policy.
Close Banner
